<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>welcome on Wedding of David and Emma Rappeport</title>
    <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/tags/welcome/</link>
    <description>Recent content in welcome on Wedding of David and Emma Rappeport</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/tags/welcome/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Rappeport Family</title>
      <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/rappeports/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/rappeports/</guid>
      <description>Rappeports Photo 1 - Photo taken at a wedding celebration hosted by Brenda and Scott for David and Emma at Oakledge in Sunapee, New Hampshire. David&amp;rsquo;s brother Emma was also there. Photo 2 - David and Eric after hiking Long&amp;rsquo;s Peak together in Estes Park, Colorado. Photo 3 - David, Eric, Scott, and Emma at the annual Mt. Sunapee duck drop in October 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fleming Family</title>
      <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/flemings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/flemings/</guid>
      <description>Flemings Photo 1 - Christmas with the Flemings. Grandpa Jim, Granny Rudina, Pauline Fleming, David Fleming, Emma Fleming 1, Emma Fleming 2, David Rappeport, Claire Fleming. Photo 2 - Emma and Claire at their older brother David&amp;rsquo;s wedding. Photo 3 - Emma, Clair, Pauline, and Hugo walking in Brooklyn in early February 2024. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Fleming</title>
      <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/david-fleming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/david-fleming/</guid>
      <description>Emma&amp;rsquo;s Father Photo 1 - Emma and her father, David Fleming, at a restaurant in Phoenix, Arizona. Photo 2 - David was an avid hiker and runner. This is a photo of Emma and David together on a hike in northern Arizona. Photo 3 - David used to run up Piestawa Peak in Phoenix Arizona every weekend. Dave took this photo from the summit after making the same run while visiting with Emma&amp;rsquo;s family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We eloped last year</title>
      <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/elopement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/elopement/</guid>
      <description>So yes, we&amp;rsquo;re already married Photo 1 - Action shot with a view from the top of the courthouse in Santa Barbara, California. Photo 2 - In front of the courthouse minutes after getting married. Photo 3 - Holding hands while taking care of the wedding paperwork. Photo 4 - Dave holding up the wedding contract as proof of a legal marriage contract. He couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more thrilled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yeah so we got engaged</title>
      <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/proposal/</guid>
      <description>Obviously she said yes Photo 1 - Champagne toast at L&amp;rsquo;Auberge de Sedona right after Dave&amp;rsquo;s super secret amazing proposal. Photo 2 - Engagement photos on top of a mountain in Sedona the day after getting engaged. Photo 3 - Second photo from the same site of the photo shoot the day after our engagement. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penny and Rhubarb Appreciation Photos</title>
      <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/penny-and-rhubarb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/penny-and-rhubarb/</guid>
      <description>The Loves of our Lives Photo 1 - Penny and Rhubarb at Domino park at sunset. Photo 2 - Baby Rhubarb eating dinner with us at DOC wine bar next to our apartment in Williamsburg. Photo 3 - Baby Penny next to a statue in her likeness in Rittenhouse Square, Philadelphia. Photo 4 - Penny, Rhubarb, and Emma on Roosevelt Island during a summer picnic. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All our friends</title>
      <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/all-of-our-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/all-of-our-friends/</guid>
      <description>Amazing people, Amazing memories Photo 1 - The view from mid mountain. Enjoying a mid day apres at La Flegere with Kelly, Marisa, Bariscan, and Brent. Photo 2 - Days after first moving to NYC from Philadelphia, Bariscan, Dave, and Emma at the finish of the Brooklyn Half Marathon. Photo 3 - Dave, Emma, Kelly, and Jeff. Kelly and Jeff spending the day with us in Brooklyn at Domino Park. Photo 4 - Dave, Claire, and Max sailing around Manhattan on a crisp Fall afternoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sitting on a dock by the bay with you</title>
      <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/boat-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/boat-photos/</guid>
      <description>Aspiring boat people Photo 1 - Sailing off the coast of Camden, Maine the day of Dave&amp;rsquo;s 30th birthday. Photo 2 - This photo was taken just after Emma and Dave completed their open water scuba diving certification in the Florida Keys. Photo 3 - Sunset photo taken from the back of the Lake Sunapee Dinner Cruise boat. Photo 4 - An ocean pontoon ride courtesy of our friends Sarah Noe and Dan Biscobing the day after their wedding in Hawaii.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>She broadens my horizons</title>
      <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/traveling-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/traveling-together/</guid>
      <description>Traveling Photo 1 - Dave and Emma in Ankor Wat, Cambodia. Photo 2 - Together on a hike in Zion National Park during the middle of Covid. Photo 3 - On a chairlift at Snowbird, Utah. Emma, always willing to try new things, took up skiing after first meeting me because she knew it was one of my great passions in life. Photo 4 - Cool couple shot! Our tour guide in Ankor Wat insisted on this photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stand by me</title>
      <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/supporting-eachother/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/supporting-eachother/</guid>
      <description>Couple Goals Photo 1 - Dave and Emma at Emma&amp;rsquo;s law school graduation. Photo 2 - Dave and Emma after Dave completes his first marathon. Photo 3 - Dave and Emma together at the top of Mt. Washington, New Hampshire. This photo was taken on our second attempt at the summit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I can tell that we are gonna be friends.</title>
      <link>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/date-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.dave-and-emma-wedding.com/photos/welcome/date-nights/</guid>
      <description>Date Nights Photo 1 - One of our very first dates together in Philadelphia. Who won at Jenga is still a contentious subject. Photo 2 - Date night overlooking the NYC skyline in Williamsburg New York. Photo 3 - Holiday night at with friend&amp;rsquo;s at Rolf&amp;rsquo;s NYC. Photo 4 - Another holiday date night this time at the Brooklyn Botanical Gardens Lightscape.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
